export const quizQuestions_9 = {
  questions: [
  {
    question: 'What is array destructuring in JavaScript?',
    choices: [
      'A method to create arrays from multiple variables',
      'A way to extract values from arrays into distinct variables',
      'A technique to combine arrays into a single variable',
      'A method to check if a variable is an array'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'A way to extract values from arrays into distinct variables'
  },
  {
    question: 'How is array destructuring commonly used in React components?',
    choices: [
      'To create arrays from React props',
      'To iterate through arrays in JSX',
      'To extract values from arrays passed as props or state',
      'Array destructuring is not supported in React'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'To extract values from arrays passed as props or state'
  },
  {
    question: 'What does object destructuring enable in JavaScript?',
    choices: [
      'To combine multiple objects into a single object',
      'To extract properties from objects into distinct variables',
      'To create objects from multiple variables',
      'To check if a variable is an object'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'To extract properties from objects into distinct variables'
  },
  {
    question: 'How is object destructuring beneficial in React development?',
    choices: [
      'To avoid creating objects in React components',
      'To create objects from React props',
      'To simplify access to nested object properties in props or state',
      'Object destructuring is not used in React'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'To simplify access to nested object properties in props or state'
  },
  {
    question: 'In React, what is the syntax for array destructuring used with props?',
    choices: [
      'const [value] = props;',
      'const { value } = props;',
      'const (value) = props;',
      'const <value> = props;'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'const { value } = props;'
  },
  {
    question: 'When using object destructuring in React, how do you extract nested object properties?',
    choices: [
      'By using multiple destructuring statements',
      'By specifying the path to the nested property directly in the destructuring syntax',
      'By using an array for nested properties',
      'Object destructuring does not support nested properties'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'By specifying the path to the nested property directly in the destructuring syntax'
  },
  {
    question: 'What happens if the object or array does not contain the specified property or index during destructuring?',
    choices: [
      'It throws an error',
      'It assigns the value `undefined` to the variable',
      'It creates a new variable with an empty value',
      'It skips the destructuring and moves to the next variable'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'It assigns the value `undefined` to the variable'
  },
  {
    question: 'Can you rename variables while using destructuring in JavaScript?',
    choices: [
      'No, renaming is not supported in destructuring',
      'Yes, by using the `rename` keyword',
      'Yes, by specifying a new variable name using the `:` syntax',
      'Only objects support renaming in destructuring'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Yes, by specifying a new variable name using the `:` syntax'
  },
  {
    question: 'Is it possible to provide default values while using destructuring?',
    choices: [
      'No, destructuring cannot handle default values',
      'Yes, by using the `=` syntax with the variable',
      'Only arrays support default values in destructuring',
      'Default values can only be set for the first variable in destructuring'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Yes, by using the `=` syntax with the variable'
  },
  {
    question: 'What happens if you attempt to destructure a non-iterable or non-existent value in JavaScript?',
    choices: [
      'It throws an error',
      'It assigns the value `null` to the variable',
      'It assigns an empty value to the variable',
      'It skips the destructuring and moves to the next variable'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'It throws an error'
    },
  ],
}





